Ouja
<Battling with the strongest king Dundee
Aim
Target Satoshi.
Got all the pockets to
one
Dream
is also
Go has a dream to get there.
Futari
This is the life and adventure of these two people
Monogatari
is a story to draw>
(Pikachu) Pika Pika!
(map) Ma~! Ma!
Today
is
<Today's weather is fine
An idyllic holiday＞
(Koharu)? Already!
Mado
Oto
(sound hitting the window)
(out) That's right....
This is Mom's illust.
(Yoshino)?
Wa
Musume
(Yoshino) There are... My daughter as expected.
I
This is me, right?
Oh….
I
Keiya
then
Normal
I wonder if I know and make it an ordinary.
This is a character
Creativity.
Zenzen
to
It doesn't look like Koharu at all.
Which which?
Hey
(Out) My sister!
See!
If you don't like it...
(Wampapchi) Wanpampampa!
yo
What
What? Winch.
Oh!
What
What? What are you holding?
or
Hey, wait a minute.
(Sakura) Won Pachi This.
OK, OK.
(out) This is a map.
Oh, but...
Ego
Doesn't work.
(Wampa) Wampa!
OK
It's ok
I'm just faint.
Good.
By the way,
Mado
What
Something hit the window.
It must have been this map.
Kur!
Wampa!
Ma-Kuru-Kuru-!
(everyone) Oh...
Kur….
You're playing the game.
Hey, let's take care of it.
and
Until this child can fly.
I
Let me take care of you.
TEA
Saki
Allowance first.
.
< This is Sakura Park.
Today
Satoshi is still
Asa
Tokkun
Special training from the morning on Pomon Battle >
(Rio) All!
Pica!
Chu!
u
and
(Satoshi) Please take it!
Rio!
Pica!
pica~!
Futari
Nice to see you both!
Next
Okay, next….
(Go) Satoshi!
mi
You didn't see it?
pica?
mi
What? I haven't seen it.
is gone.
mi
Also? Not just invisible?
Main
Think
is
I searched for various things...
Yeah? I was there!
That!
(Barrier) Barry!
What's the barrier or
check
mi
Eventually I couldn't find it.
(rabbit) Bif….
I
is
Okay, let's find the messon too.
Pica!
Rio!
na
Goe
(crying)
Go!
Yeah.
Goe
(crying)
This is….
The message is here...
Absolutely!
Message Where are you?
Yes!
butterflies Molfon Numbness!
Goe
(crying)
(Messon) Some~!
Pica!
was there.
(Strike) Strike!
Something~!
The usual one for Kyrie Messon!
Me~!
Me… Meso.
frequently
Great appetite.
.
Curl...Foot.
Is it a feast?
I
Mapapato me-souta.
Hey
This is
to Koharu-neechan
To
Dad and mom.
Curl….
Wampa Wampa.
Oh….
Mamephat This child is a witch.
Wampa.
Curl~!
or
Wait here and there.
Kur~!
Oh, okay.
or
Wait, wait.
W/W
Oh
Witch Punch You can't chase.
Kur~ Kur~!
Curl...
Wampa.
One-on!
Kur~!
Wampa….
What do you mean?
Senaka
Mamepato has a wacky back
Yes
I like it.
Until a while ago
I was afraid of the punch?
What makes me scared is
Forget
I've forgotten it already.
(3 people) Yeah!?
Map
Yes
What the trainer says
Sunao
I honestly ask, but
Muzuka
Shinji
The difficult instructions are
Rikai
Sometimes I don't understand
Forget
Very forgetful
Meirei
Forget
I'll soon forget it.
What
What a cute thing!
That's cute.
Cute... Kana?
Wampa.
It might be cute.
Wampa!
Regards, Mapate.
Jibun
No
Main
Think of it as your own home
Please slow down.
Wampa Wampa….
punch?
Curl~ Curl~
Wampa! Wampa...
Kuru... Kuru?
Click kl~!
Yeah? Welcome mape.
Circle... …
Kuru Kuru... Kuru~!
only
Want to see it?
Curl~!
Oh….
Kuru-Kuru-Kuru-Kuru!
Joshi
ha… Class Girl
only
Only
You're looking at it quite a bit.
Curl….
s
Do you like it? Mojamoja.
Kuru-Kuru-Kuru-Kuru-.
s
Do you like it?
～
Cru... Cruck Cru....
Wow!
Wampa Wampa.
It's pretty.
Curl….
～
(out) Cute Mameput.
was
Eat a lot.
yesterday
Map Map from yesterday
Genki
Have you been well?
Wampa Wampa….
seifuku
Hey Wanpachi Uniform
Yabu
If it breaks,
punch?
What's wrong?
I have to be a gerah.
Jerase?
Wa
and
(Sakura) Wampapachi is
at home
Sue
Sonzai
Existence like the youngest.
From all the family
(Yoshino) Right.
is now
Sue
Tachibana
Uba
The youngest child's position is deprived of by Mape
chair
Even my favorite coral is
I'm very interested in mappate.
I see.
I don't know.
To
Dad time to go out.
Yes!
Today
Maigo
is
Today I'm looking for a lost mappant
Whether or not there is a trainer
Shira
Check it out.
Nega
Thank you.
Wampa Wampa...
Curl~!
Yes
I really liked it.
Two people
(two people).
Gill
Great Punch
It looks like a maple brother.
That's good.
shochu
What
(range) Director What is
Is this all right?
yesterday
the maple gagged yesterday
Hogo
Protected.
Mado
It seems that you hit the window glass.
Now
SN
That information is now uploaded to SNS.
Maigo
Kanousei
There is a possibility of getting lost in a pomon.
I see.
Before
(Kikuna) It was in front of me.
Mado
Don on the window.
(range) If it is a transparent glass,
Tori Pomons
There are times when you don't notice it.
Sai
Fortunately then
Without much
and
I flew again soon.
(End-time team)
Today
What
What do you do after school today?
is
to search for a pomon
Minato
Yes
Let's go to the port.
Okay.
Haya
《Kohal: Mamepato, quickly and like that
Sora
and
Would you like to fly in the sky?
Hey, let's take care of it.
and
Until this child can fly
Until I can fly...
pica!
Curl~!
shiny!
tomorrow
See you tomorrow.
Wampa Wampa….
Right now, a punching maple.
Wampa Wampa!
Curl~!
Curl….
shiny!
What's wrong?
Wampa Wampa….
What's that Koharu Jan?
Shocho
Y
What the boss said was
Mappe?
Wampa Wampa….
open patter?
Curl~!
Wampa….
What do you mean?
Giraffe.
(Satoshi/Go) Jerase?
The pitch is
Petting the map
I'm jealous.
(Satoshi/Go) Yakimochi?
I
to both the pitch and the maple
I'm touching in the same way.
Wampa Wampa….
Hana
if the maple is apart from Koharu
Is that all right?
.
It's a lot of hassle with the jail.
Yes
Well don't say that.
Chii
Kura
Wrapper's jerk
Cute Monsa.
to ?
?
Obo
I remember Koharu-chan at that time.
Yeah!?
I
shochu
I'm still the director
When I was a student...
Chiho
s
Yujin
From a friend who lives in the Gallar region
Put
A letter was sent to you.
u
Before the birth of the
alone
The only child is
Moist
I was very jealous of the punch.
I
I?
To
Dad and Mom
Main
Koharu-chan at that time.
Range Mr. Wan Pachi
Cute crap!
I
to me.
Yes
Did you say that?
I can't remember at all.
Chiho
but
polls in the Gal region are
Mezura
Because it's rare
only
Where Koharu-chan doesn't see
Shira
For example, check out the information about the punch line.
To
Dad and Mom
Before
in front of the coral
Don't pet the embrace
I was careful.
is
Somehow embarrassing
Too childish.
Common things
is
I'm not shy.
By the way, Kikuna-san.
I
Bai
Younger sister
I used to be my sister, but
Taisho
This is the target of the jarrage.
Naka
How did you get along?
Koharu and open space.
One day, the corals are in a narrow space
Yes
I said this.
yes
I wish I could go somewhere.
I
Wow Worst past me.
Oh
happened after that.
(Satoshi/Go) Incident?
(Sakura) Wampa Pachi runaway incident.
Noe
Runaway...
Yes
I wish I could go somewhere!
Wampa….
Ah…
What
(Sakura) What happened?
Yes
(Yoshino) Where did you go?
What's wrong?
I don't have any punches.
Would you like a punch?
OK
It's okay.
To
is
My dad will go looking for it.
Mod
Good night back to your bed.
Look, it's a punch.
Wampa Wampa….
Goe
(crying)
Damn it!
No!
Wampa Wampa.
Wrap...…
punch!
Where?
Yes
Where? Where did you go
(Comp) COMP COMP...
Goe
(crying)
I
Oh
I chasing a punch…
I'm afraid of companion...
Main
Remember?
Then there was a punch...
COMP COMP COMP….
Wampa Wampa….
Wicky Wanpachi
Tickling
(Sakura) From then on.
to
Only in a room with a punch
ne
Sleepless
Only Pomon Foods prepared by Kohal
was
I stopped eating.
Wouldn't it be nice to have a patchwork?
Jibun
Kohal
is
You've come to find me.
(Wampachee) Wampampwamp….
Open Pitch!?
(Originally) Ah!
Wampa Wampa….
Oh!
Cru... Cru!
Ma~!
Wampa Wampa….
Kur~!
Unique!
Wampampamper!
Wampa.
Wampa Power Pumper!
Wrap...…
shochu
Director I have to do something.
Maka
Let's leave it to Koharu and Wanpachi.
Eh!?
Oh!
Wampa Pampa!
Shit
Naka
Koharu Wampa Pachi Jealous
Before
If you work together
enough
Should be able to fight enough air.
Dad...
Gambaba
Good luck Koharu!
shiny!
Go!
Oh!
I'm gonna go out!
Wampa!
Oh!
Spark!
Kur~!
I did it!
has been decided!
shiny!
Bif.
Kur~!
Kur….
Wampa Wampa….
Oh!
Wampamp Wampamp On!
Oh, it's unique!
or
Hey, wait a second!
Oh~
Bif.
pica.
haha….
This time our map is
wrinkles
Thank you very much.
Really
Rei
May I thank you...
I
The coin is
of my maple trace team.
It's a leader.
(4 people) Leader!?
Haya
Speed is fast and
Naka
Momo
Kimo
Feelings of trying to protect fellows are
Who
Tsuyo
Stronger than anyone.
Tagui
An exceptional leadership
also
Nushi
I'm the owner.
Was that?
Mapper, are you going?
Yes
really
Kaede
I'm going back to the real house of Mape.
Thank you for loving me.
Naka
Even though I've made good friends...
Sorter.
?
mi
Look at the map.
really
The map is a real trainer
chair
I love you.
That's right.
Wampaphone Wampa!
Aso
Mamepato Please come and play again.
or
I'm waiting.
Kuru~Kuru~!
Shizu
Quiet, if you don't have a mapto.
Only 2 days….
Two people
(2 people).
To
or
Only
(Koharu) Is this the book that Dad wrote?
(Yoshino) Yes.
Muzuka
(Koharu) It seems difficult.
Only
Hit this book
together
A human and a pomon stay together
was
What to do in the world
or
is written.
together
A human and a pomon stay together
was
How to live a happy life...
Shit
Naka
Koharu Wampa Pachi Jealous
Before
If you work together
enough
should be able to fight enough air
What a cool dad.
That's cool.
then
Didn't you know?
<
with mappate
Waka
key
Experience encounters and parting
Kyori
Chika
One step closer to the pomon
was a coral>